

Contacts

+38 063 106 59 86

sdubovyi@yahoo.com

Telegram

Linkedin

GitHub

Ukraine, Kyiv

Tech skills

- HTML
- CSS / SCSS
- JS
- React
- Github
- Figma
- Postman
- API integration
- Google firebase
- Node
- MongoDB

Soft skills

- Autonomy
- Creativity
- Continuous Learning
- Problem-Solving

Languages

English - Pre-Intermediate

Ukraine - Native

Russian - Native

Oleksandr Dubovyi

Junior Front-end developer

Summary

I am a beginner in front-end development, currently undergoing training at Golt's Front- End Developer Bootcamp. I have experience working with JavaScript, React, HTML, CSS/SCSS, Git/GitHub, and utilizing libraries for coding and working with APIs. I am responsible and creative, with a strong willingness to learn and explore new technologies in programming.

Project experience

Budget Boss | Link [REACT, JS, STYLED-COMPONENTS, REST API]

- All visual aspects: CSS, styled components, animations.
- Modal Windows implementation.
- Writing code for the header, home page, and report page.

Bookshelf | Link [HTML, JS, SCSS, REST API, GOOGLE FIREBASE]

- Writing code for the main page of the website.
- · Working with the API.
- · User authentication with Google Firebase.

Sweet Chocolate | Link [HTML, CSS, JS]

- All visual aspects: CSS, animations.
- Writing code for the main page, "IT ALL ADDS UP TO ONE EXCEPTIONAL TASTE SENSATION" section and modal windows.
- · Organizing teamwork and assigning tasks.

Work experience

'Unicum Alliance'

2020-2023

Financial Consultant:

- · Strengthened client relationships through proactive communication, leading to increased satisfaction and client retention.
- Implemented a comprehensive system for tracking and analyzing client data, improving decision-making processes, and providing customized service.
- · Orchestrated successful client meetings, demonstrating excellent interpersonal skills and effectively addressing client needs.
- Developed innovative trading strategies that generated significant returns and contributed to business growth.
- Led teams of 10 and 40 members as Team Lead and Desk Manager respectively, achieving high productivity and goal attainment.
- · Designed comprehensive onboarding webinars for new employees, facilitating smooth transitions and integration.

'CraftFood, Mondeleze'

2019-2020

Trade Representative:

- Increased product visibility and brand awareness through effective presentations and displays.
- Negotiated favorable shelf placements, resulting in improved sales and product
- Implemented efficient inventory management strategies, reducing stockouts and improving product availability.
- Consistently achieved sales targets through persuasive techniques and effective communication of product benefits.

Education

'GoIT'

Full Stack Developer

Skills: HTML, CSS/SCSS, JS, React, GitHub, Figma, Postman, API Integration

'Institute of Innovative Education, Kyiv National University of Construction and Architecture'

Bachelor's Degree

Occupational Safety in Construction

2012 - 2017

'Kyiv College of Construction, Architecture, and Design'

Building and Structure Furnishing and Construction Design

2008 - 2012